- What the hell are you doing, sis?
- Working out.
- Why?
- No idea.
You’re Team GP, right?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
You’ll be going on stage in ten minutes.
Please get ready.
What did he say?
We go on in ten minutes.
Sis, I’m gonna go check first.
You okay?
Yeah.
I
I like you.
And...
do you like me?
Do you still think I’m mad
because you play games?
I’m mad because you lied to me.
You wanted to follow your dream.
See that dream?
It all burned to ashes.
I’m sorry
for pulling you into my dream
without ever asking what you wanted.
You okay, Kao?
Yeah, I’m good.
Guys.
Hey, do you remember
the qualifiers three months ago?
Back then, it was brutal.
It took everything we had
just to make it into the Pro League.
And a team of old-timers like us
we were total underdogs
from day one.
But not today.
Because today
we’re the dark horse.
If we’ve made it this far
then there’s nothing left to be scared of.
GP
Are we fighting or not?
- We are.
- Yeah.
Woo! GP! GP! GP!
Welcome, honored guests
to the fiercest
and biggest competition we’ve ever had.
And this is the WOG Pro League
for the 2025 season.
And of course
this season’s WOG Pro League
brings together top-tier players
from all over the country
as always, featuring top teams such as
it’s MYSTIC a team stacked with elite talent
or PONYTALE
who have placed in the top three
for three straight seasons.
And this year they’ve also brought in
a world-class coach from China
to strengthen the team even more.
And of course,
we can’t leave out MADDOX
the reigning champions,
packed with national team players.
And this year, they’ve also added
a devastatingly skilled player.
And with Methat joining the squad this year
one thing’s for sure
his team is strong in every position.
And last but not least,
our rookie team.
Team GP.
Led by their captain, Tep G
a name already talked about
throughout the gaming world.
And today,
we’ll finally get to witness their skills
on this very stage.
Are you ready
for this brand-new season?
And here comes
our first match of the season.
Are you ready?
Shit, that’s a huge crowd.
Holy shit, I’m gonna piss myself.
What?
Forget it.
Let’s go. Come on.
Go.
Hurry up.
Wait a sec.
We’re in a hurry, asshole.
No matter what happens
give it everything you’ve got.
Everyone
just stick to the plan.
Go, go, go.
And now,
the match is about to begin.
That’s right
3 2 1
Go, go, go.
GP really drew a tough one
for their opening match.
They’re up against
one of our Pro League favorites PONYTALE.
Alright, this match
is getting more intense by the second.
Absolutely incredible, everyone.
Did you see that?
That game ended in the blink of an eye.
- Amazing.
- Wow, I can’t believe it.
That right there has to be the play of the day.
And let me remind you PONYTALE is a top-three team.
MYSTIC
Let’s move on
to the next match now.
Yes.
MYSTIC is already engaging.
That’s right.
Watch closely here watch closely.
And, and, and
with a performance like this
it’s safe to say
Tep G and Gunslinger God
are absolutely the real deal.
Goodbye.
Hell yeah.
And now we’ve reached
our grand final.
At last, we now know
that this year’s championship match
will be a clash of powerhouse teams.
A team made up of veteran players
with all the experience to match their style.
That team
is none other than MADDOX.
And the rookie challengers
everyone’s been watching.
GP
Which team will it be?
One of these two teams
will take the championship
and the 18-million-baht prize.
So stay tuned we’ll know the winner
by the end of the weekend.
See you then.
Alright, everyone, listen up.
MADDOX is a team
that likes to play fast and go for early kills.
If we stay focused on defense
and hit back fast,
I know we can beat them.
And Tep G
go in fast, get out fast.
Don’t die for nothing.
Every team that’s lost to MADDOX
they all made the same mistake
They rushed in and kept giving away free deaths.
You can trust Tep G.
Guys
I posted it in the group.
Momon-chan’s sponsoring MADDOX now.
Just let him go.
We’re on different paths now.
We fight our own fight.
Wasn’t he GP’s former sponsor?
Yeah.
Since before we got into the Pro League.
That’s bad.
He knows every style we practiced
every trick we’ve ever used.
Shit, sis,
it’s like we got brain-hacked.
Then we change the plan.
Everyone, go sort out
your personal business now.
After this,
no one leaves this room again.
Come on, sis. Let’s go.
You sure this is a good idea?
Yeah, come on. Let’s go.
Go on, go in.
The house has changed a lot.
Wrong house, bro.
- Let’s go.
- Hey, wait.
What brings you here today, son?
Work? Or your wife?
Phan.
I’m sorry, Mom.
Ow.
Why does my whole body hurt?
What are you doing? Need help?
No, I’m good.
I’m almost done.
Why?
You scared you might catch feelings for me?
She’s not catching feelings.
She’s annoyed.
No.
I’m not annoyed.
I’m just uncomfortable.
You’re not scared
you’re gonna make me cry saying that?
You assholes.
Guys
if we actually win this thing
what happens after that?
I never even thought that far.
I think I’ll probably retire
from being a pro player.
My back hurts.
I’m old. I can’t keep doing this.
And you
when you go study abroad,
don’t forget us, okay?
Come on,
how could I forget you guys?
I’m going to study, not dying.
True.
I think
after this, we probably won’t get
to sit around playing games like this again.
Why?
What, are we gonna die?
Just kidding.
You never know.
The future’s uncertain.
I love you guys.
Since the day we met.
I’ve never said it before
but all the time I’ve spent with you guys.
- I’ve.
- I’ve been happy too.
When we’re old, come back
and play games together once in a while, alright?
Mm.
Oh, shit I’m gonna cry.
Nope. Let’s go eat.
Shit, I’m seriously gonna cry.
Then cry.
Why would I cry? Hell no.
That’s embarrassing.
Hey, just kidding.
I’m messing with you.
Kao: Hope your new project goes well.
Kao: I’m rooting for you.
Rapee: Bring home the championship.
Rapee: I’m rooting for you too.
- Kao: Thank you.
- Rapee: Thank you.
These last three days
will decide everything we’ve worked for.
This round is a Best of 3.
Whoever takes game one
has the biggest edge.
Kao.
I want you to try sniping.
Are you messing with me?
If you put me on sniper and pin me down like that,
how am I supposed to survive?
Just trust me.
MADDOX
is gonna lock onto you
from game one.
It’s okay.
Don’t worry about getting pinned down.
I’ll show you myself
just how aggressive
a sniper can play.
There’s a match tomorrow.
Are you coming to cheer us on?
It’s just that
Mr. Rapee
the international department
is requesting an urgent meeting.
Then I should get going.
P’Phan, P’Phan.
Tell Kao something for me.
Tell Kao
to bring home the championship.
I’m counting on you.
Pee.
Wouldn’t it be better
if you told Kao yourself?
I’m heading out. See you.
Today, the two of us
will be your hosts
for the fiercest and most intense match of all
because this is the Finals
of the WOG Pro League Season 2025.
And today’s a huge matchup.
MADDOX versus GP.
Both teams have been on fire
since round one.
Now we’ll see
who takes the prize money and the right
to reach the summit first.
Wow, world championship level.
Oh.
- But right now.
- Yes.
Judging by the atmosphere today,
there’s only one thing to say
the crowd lining up
outside the arena right now
is massive.
And the energy right now
is absolutely electric.
Look at that people even brought their kids.
The place is packed.
Hey, have they started yet?
F you wanna know,
go in and see for yourself.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Smartass.
This is a staff pass You can get anywhere with it.
And this is the cap.
Don’t let anyone see your face
Don’t let anyone recognize you.
And this shirt put it on
so you look like everyone else.
Here’s your pay Now go.
Shit.
Excuse me.
Hey, guys where’s this place?
Oh, you came to watch the match too?
Where’s this?
Find it yourself, man.
You better watch it.
Go back to your seat.
Ow, ow, ow.
P’Pee.
Come down here.
Huh?
Yeah, come down. Hurry.
Don’t be so slow.
Your legs are long.
- What is it?
- Momon.
Momon what?
Momon the other team’s sponsor
I saw him doing something weird.
What?
He’s cheating.
Go check backstage.
Do whatever you have to do.
Just go find out. Go.
Excuse me
it’s almost match time.
Five minutes till the match starts.
Please head up and get ready.
Alright, Let me handle the team first.
Go check backstage too.
- Right this way,
- Thank you
you can’t stay here.
You need to go back to your seat.
- Oh, okay.
- Thank you
I don’t know where it is.
It’s over there.
P’Kao P’Kao.
Where have you been?
The match is about to start. Hurry.
- Get to your spots, quick.
- P’Kao.
Go sit down first.
Both teams, please stand by.
The match is about to begin.
If anyone is not present,
it will be considered a forfeit.
Thank you.
Kao.
Kao, I need to talk to you.
What is it, P’Pee?
Yeah, and just now
Pete was saying.
What? I couldn’t hear you
Pete said Momon’s cheating or something.
P’Pee, we’ll talk later.
I’m about to play.
Momon’s cheating.
No seats left, sir?
Upstairs, upstairs hurry.
The show’s starting. You can’t stand here.
Toey? Toey, where’d you go?
Go check backstage.
Can you go check backstage for me?
Okay.
The control room’s in the back.
Hurry up, the show’s about to start.
Let me remind everyone first
this Finals match will be played.
It's going to be a Best of 3.
That means
whoever wins two out of three first
takes the title
and the championship.
Stick to the plan, alright?
Guys
listen.
As long as Tep G dies
the rest are nothing.
Let’s go.
He’s really skinny now
I asked him
what he’d been eating to get that skinny.
Wanna know what he said?
He said he had cancer.
How the hell did he know I was here?
Shit, he knows way too much.
How the hell does he know
where Kao’s going?
Asshole.
Yeah, something’s definitely off.
That’s right.
Things are looking pretty worrying right now.
Tep G is really getting swarmed.
Looks like today.
Team GP fans
are gonna have to cheer extra hard.
Because today,
nothing seems to be going Team GP’s way.
Who the hell are you?
Oh.
Pat, what the hell is wrong with you?
Your hands are so weak
You die way too easily.
Damn it, asshole.
Okay, very good
Yeah, just like that.
Two of them are dead already
Okay.
Last night was insane, man.
So damn good.
- Really?
- For real.
Hey.
Aon.
Which Aon?
- Yeah, which Aon?
- Uh.
Wake Aon up!
Bro, Aon
I don’t know
what the hell he ate
but he’s passed out naked in the room
with swollen eyes like this.
Damn.
Who the hell are you?
- Uh.
Who is it?
Uh... eat...
Shrimp.
- Shrimp.
What the hell?
River prawns.
- River prawns.
- Oh, shit
- screwed.
- Go after him.
With a stomp like that,
GP can kiss this game goodbye.
Goodbye! Hiyah.
Wow, everyone
just as expected.
That means MADDOX
has taken game one
against GP.
I’ve gotta say.
Team GP’s fans
must be on edge right now.
As for match two,
all I can say is
it’s been fierce and intense.
So far,
there haven’t been any kills at all.
Don’t rush, guys
Listen to me. Listen carefully.
Okay, everyone?
Okay, slow down. Slow down.
They’ve gotta be really careful here, because
if GP slips up for even a second in this game,
it could mean losing it all for good.
That’s right.
Where is?
Shit
my gun won’t fire at all.
What the hell? Why is it lagging like this?
Shit, I’m dead again. Goddamn it.
Oh.
- They’re pushing.
- Here they come.
- Here we go, GP.
- Can GP survive this? Can they survive?
Who is it?
Aon.
You just walked in without making a sound.
Didn’t even knock, asshole.
Sorry, sorry, sorry
I was just getting into it.
You two carry on
I’ll go check the system.
I’m definitely not looking.
Go ahead, go ahead.
What the hell are you doing?
Aon, get over here.
You’re dead.
Bro, bro, it’s me Aon.
Today’s my first day interning here.
Maybe you don’t recognize me yet?
- Listen, Aon. Remember this.
- Don’t mess with me.
I’m not messing around.
It’s really my first day.
Don’t look so scary.
- They’re pushing.
- Here they come.
- Here we go, GP.
- Can GP survive this? Can they survive?
Jordan.
- You like them too?
- Yeah.
You’re a Jordan guy, huh.
- Jordan? Seriously?
- Yeah.
Do you remember 98? 98?
He was dribbling it down
with time running out. Time was running out.
- Man, that last shot.
- Hat one got me. Shoot, shoot, shoot.
That shot swish.
That win’s stayed with me
ever since.
Goodbye.
Pee tum nah bplook kao ruk naung sao gaem reua
(I work harvesting rice, I love my pale-faced girl)
Naung bpen sao nah gleua
(I’m a salt pond girl)
Noom nah kao mai taut ting
(Rice farming men won’t abandon you)
Tah pee ja bpai kor bpai kor por ja wah yahng rai
(If I went and asked, asked your father, what would he say?)
norng sut saen diijai thaa phii pai khor norng jingjing
(I'd be so incredibly happy if you really asked for my hand)
num naakhaau rap-rorng mai thortthing
(The rice farmer boy promises never to leave you)
thaa rak norng jingjing
(If you truly love me, )
yaa thing saau naakluea
(please don't abandon this salt farm girl)
- Hey.
- Hey, what the hell?
- What’s going on?
- Oh.
- Whoa.
Yes.
- What’s happening?
- Ladies and gentlemen
it looks like the match
has run into a slight issue
with the lighting system.
There’s been a minor power issue.
Oh, oh, oh.
Our staff is working on it
as quickly as possible.
Please bear with us for a moment.
I’ve just gotten a message
coming in from viewers at home.
They’re saying, Don’t raise
the lights like that, it’s scary.
Alright then,
we’ll keep it like this.
Everyone.
Come talk to me for a second.
That’s right, P’Phan.
When I went to the bathroom
I saw Momon talking to someone,
and he was acting really weird
I tried to warn you guys
but the match started first.
Where have you been?
The match is about to start. Hurry up.
Get to your spots.
From here on out,
it’s all down to skill.
There’s no way
they can cheat us anymore.
You know
what matters most on a team?
Teamwork.
And you know
what beats teamwork?
Family.
I believe
that our GP family
can beat MADDOX.
So, are we fighting or not?
Okay.
The power’s back.
Alright, everyone,
the match is back on.
Our staff has confirmed
- that the lighting issue has been resolved.
- That’s right.
And now we’re ready
for the next game.
Both teams, please stand by.
And to everyone watching
let’s cheer them on together.
Let me remind you once again
for game two
which is about to begin
if MADDOX wins this one
if they take the win
hat means this year’s Pro League trophy
will stay in the hands
of the reigning champions, MADDOX.
Let’s see
whether the rookies, GP
can turn things around this time.
Whoa.
I’m telling you
this is going to be an absolute nail-biter
- Go, go, go, go.
There are two of them
camping in the house.
Okay, okay I’m on my way.
- Don’t rush. Listen to me. Listen carefully.
- Their plan is no joke.
Oh that hit hard.
Tep G has already landed a hit.
Fall back, fall back they’re coming in from behind
I told you to fall back. Yeah.
That hit full on.
Whoa.
I’ve gotta say,
this match is insane. Absolutely insane.
If anyone stepped out to pee,
you definitely missed out.
Alright, let’s keep watching.
Hey, don’t rush it.
Listen to me.
Okay, it’s fine.
The rest of you, stay calm
and do what I say.
Okay.
Hey, I told you not to rush.
Fall back first.
Whoa, Tep G.
Tep G is in top form today.
After an intense, edge-of-your-seat game
the goddess of victory
belongs to Team GP.
- Yeah.
Game two is over.
The score is now tied at
- one to one.
- One to one.
Go, Kao, sweetheart!
Oh!
Tep G! Tep G!
Let’s go!
I’m cheering! I’m cheering!
Excuse me Excuse me.
Tep G! Louder!
Come on, louder!
Let’s go.
If you lose, teacher,
I’m taking points off.
Let’s go.
Come on! Cheer louder!
That means
we’re going to a final deciding game.
To determine who will become
this season’s Pro League champion.
Man, I can’t even get up to pee.
- This game’s too exciting.
- No way.
Because I already peed
right here.
That’s right.
What’s going on here?
What’s happening right now, everyone?
It looks like Tep G
is switching equipment.
I don’t know if Reflex here
can keep up
with someone using VRG.
This is the first year
that the tournament organizers
have allowed VRG
for in-game controls.
Because it’s already been proven
that the human brain
can control and react
just as fast as older devices.
Whether that’s mobile,
or keyboard and mouse, and all that.
So they’ve opened it up for use.
You know, with VRG,
even though it’s fast,
it still has a blind spot.
Because it goes against
natural human instinct.
If we’re thinking about zooming in.
You use your pinky and your ring finger
to touch your palm to zoom in.
Because it goes against
your natural instinct,
it’s harder to do
and easy to mess up.
If we’re going to use it
in the final game,
Noppakao
a Gen Y player like you
is the perfect person for it.
Hey, hey fall back first
Don’t go in alone like that. Wait for your team.
Yeah, fall back, fall back.
Looks like the situation has completely turned around.
Right now, Team GP
is launching a counterattack.
What is this?
Just walking out there with a sniper rifle
like Rambo in a Hollywood movie.
Go in.
Goodbye.
Ow.
Hiyah.
Yeah.
- Oh, amazing.
- Amazing.
And now, at long last
we have a new champion Team GP.
- Yeah.
- This feels so damn good.
GP
Hey.
You running away now?
What the hell are you talking about?
Hey.
- Hey.
- Go
I told you,
I’ve got nothing to do with this.
Hey, what the hell?
Congratulations to Team GP.
- Yeah.
- Yeah! Woo!
This is the moment of celebration.
You’ve claimed the championship title
along with the trophy
and 18 million baht in prize money.
Let’s hear it loud for GP!
Please come on up, Tep G,
as the team’s representative.
Our team captain.
And here it is your prize money totals
18 million baht.
- Yeah.
- Woo.
A historic moment
for our champions begins now.
Tep G, as the MVP
of this tournament,
and as the captain
who led your team to the title
this is your very first
championship moment.
Would you like
to say a few words?
- Kao.
- The mic, the mic.
- Go ahead.
Um.
It feels like a dream.
Gun, Pete, Phat, Phos
thank you, guys.
Thank you for staying true
and for never giving up on your dream.
Mom, Dad thank you.
Kao, your mom’s over there.
- Hahaha.
- Oh over there.
- Yeah.
- Woo.
Thank you. Thank you again.
Thank you to the whole gaming family
for making this world so much more fun.
- Yeah.
One more! One more!
And lastly.
I want to thank
the one who started this dream for me.
I always dreamed of becoming a pro player.
But once I started chasing that dream,
I realized
it wasn’t anything like I imagined.
It led me to people
I never thought I’d find.
And it made me realize that.
Kao.
Sorry, sorry, Kao.
I had something I wanted to tell you.
In this universe
you’re the best to me, Kao
how much gaming means to you
and how much you mean to me.
From
your loving husband.
I will.
- Woo.
And I realized that no matter how big a dream is.
- Aahhh.
Oh my God, you idiot.
Happy ending.
- You rolling yet?
- Come on.
And just like that,
the dream of becoming a pro player came true.
As for the next dream
it’s being your wife.
GG
Kao, everyone’s waiting.
Come on, let’s go party.
- What, party?
- Yeah.
Maybe not.
Come on, hurry up.
Go chase your next dream already.
Kao, if you ever have a little Tep G
bring them to me. I’ll train them myself.
- Oh.
- Get in, get in.
- Hurry up.
- Yeah, yeah.
So, Kanya... how’s it going?
- Hm.
- Oops.
Sorry